Now that we know what types of errors we can make when training a model,
现在我们知道了在训练模型时可能会出现什么类型的错误
in this section, we'll learn how to detect them.
在这部分 我们将学习如何检测它们
So let's recall the types of errors learned in the last section.
我们先回想一下上一部分中学到的错误类型
Here we can see our data on the model which fits it properly,
这里我们可以看到正确拟合数据的模型
which is a curve, or a polynomial of degree 2.
它是一个曲线 或者说二次多项式
It seems to fit our data well, and it will generalize well.
它看起来很好地拟合了我们的数据 也会很好地泛化
Then there's the high bias,
然后 当我们过度简化模型时
or underfitting error, obtained when we oversimplify our model.
会获得高偏差或者欠拟合错误
In this case, it's trying to fit a line, or a polynomial degree 1,
在这个例子中 它想通过我们的数据拟合一条直线
through our data.
或一次多项式
This model won't fit our data well.
这个模型不会很好地拟合我们的数据
And then there's the high variance,
以及当我们过度复杂化模型时
or overfitting error, obtained when we overcomplicate our model.
会出现高方差或过拟合错误
In this case, it's trying to fit a polynomial of degree 6 through our data.
比如在这个例子中 它尝试通过我们的数据拟合一个六次多项式
This model will fit our data perfectly, but
此模型会完美拟合我们的数据 但是
it won't generalize well to the testing set.
不会对测试集很好地泛化
So let's study the three models.
那么我们来研究这三个模型
A linear model of degree 1, a quadratic model of degree 2, and
一次线性模型、二次方程模型和
a polynomial model of degree 6.
六次多项式模型
Let's first split our data into training and testing sets.
首先我们将数据分为训练集和测试集
So the set of points with a colored center are the training set, and
彩色中心的点集为训练集
the set of points with the white center are the testing set.
白色中心的点集为测试集
The linear model gives us this line over here.
线性模型给出这条直线
Now how are we doing in terms of the training set and the testing set?
那么训练集和测试集的表现如何呢？
Well, we count the number of training errors, and we count three of them.
我们数一下训练误差的数量 计数为 3
So we conclude that the training error is three.
那么我们的结论是训练误差为 3
As for testing errors, we also have three.
对于测量误差 我们的计数也为 3
So we conclude that the testing error is also three.
所以结论是测量误差也为 3
We graph the training and testing error in this graph over here.
我们在下面的图中绘制训练误差和测试误差
Now let's repeat this process, but in the quadratic model.
现在 我们对二次方程模型重复这个过程
This model gives us a parabola over here.
此模型给我们一个抛物线
What is our training error?
那我们的训练误差是多少？
It's one, because we've misclassified one of the training points.
是 1 因为我们错误分类了一个训练点
The testing error is also one since we misclassified one testing point.
测试误差也为 1 因为我们错误分类了一个测试点
Thus, this model gave us a training error of one and a testing error of one.
因此 该模型的训练误差和测试误差均为 1
We again plot them in the graph below.
同样我们将它们绘制在下图中
Now we again repeat this process with the polynomial of degree six.
现在 我们又对六次多项式模型重复这个过程
The model gives us this curve.
此模型给我们这条曲线
Now your turn to shine.
现在轮到你来计算了
What are the training and testing errors for this model?
此模型的训练误差和测试误差是多少？